University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection 1984.0025
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Connecticut Workers And A Half Century Of Technological Change, 1930-1980, 1981-1982
  - Bossoli, Allan (24 pp.), 1981 December 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bossoli_A (Box 14, Folder 15 [39153013987542])
  - Bossoli, William (37 pp.), 1981 May 27; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bossoli_W (Box 14, Folder 16 [39153013987559])
  - Bournival, David (15 pp.), 1982 June 1; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bournival (Box 14, Folder 17 [39153013987567])
  - Boyle, Albert (14 pp.), 1981 November 11; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Boyle (Box 14, Folder 18 [39153013987575])
  - Bray, William (18 pp.), 1981 June 1; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bray (Box 14, Folder 19 [39153013987583])
  - Broderick, Michael (26 pp.), 1981 June 16; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Broderick (Box 14, Folder 20 [39153013987591])
  - Brooks, George (33 pp.), 1982 November 16; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Brooks (Box 14, Folder 21 [39153013987609])
  - Brown, Russell (24 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Brown (Box 14, Folder 22 [39153013987617])
  - Buchanan, Linda (48 pp.), 1981 July 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Buchanan (Box 14, Folder 23 [39153013987625])
  - Carey, William (46 pp.), 1982 October 15; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Carey (Box 14, Folder 24 [39153013987633])
  - Carlozzi, Josephine (5 pp.), 1982 March 6; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Carlozzi (Box 14, Box 25 [39153013987641])
  - Chesery, Joseph (18 pp.), 1981 September 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Chesery (Box 14, Folder 26 [39153013987658])
  - Ciarleglio, Mary (23 pp.), 1981 July 29; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ciarleglio (Box 14, Folder 27 [39153013987666])
  - Cockayne, Arthur (27 pp.), 1981 August 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Cockayne (Box 14, Folder 28 [39153013987674])
  - Connellan, Vincent (23 pp.), 1982 February 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Connellan (Box 14, Folder 29 [39153013987682])
  - Costa, Margaret (16 pp.), 1981 October 10; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Costa (Box 15, Folder 1 [39153013991809])
  - Cunha, William (39 pp.)
  - DeCarli, Peter (33 pp.), 1981 June 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/DeCarli (Box 15, Folder 3 [39153013991817])
  - DeCarlo, Robert (34 pp.), 1981 June 10; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/DeCarlo (Box 15, Folder 4 [39153013991965])
  - Delafose, Lawrence (15 pp.), 1981 November 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Delafrose (Box 15, Folder 5 [39153013991973])
  - DelVecchio, John (2 pp.), 1982 January 27; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/DelVecchio (Box 15, Folder 6 [39153013992120])
  - Dillon, Robert (46 pp.), 1981 June 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Dillon (Box 15, Folder 7 [39153013992138])
  - Downs, David (23 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Downs (Box 15, Folder 8 [39153013992286])
  - Driggs, John (39 pp.), 1981 October 7; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Driggs (Box 15, Folder 9 [39153013992294])
  - Driscoll, Jerry (27 pp.), 1981 June 25; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/DriscollJer (Box 15, Folder 10 [39153013992302])
  - Driscoll, John (32 pp.), 1981 December 4; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Driscoll (Box 15, Folder 11 [39153013992146])
  - Drosehn, Fred (24 pp.), 1982 January 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Drosehn (Box 15, Folder 12 [39153013991981])
  - Dubois, James (25 pp.), 1981 July 7; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Dubois (Box 15, Folder 13 [39153013991825])
  - Edwards, Larry (37 pp.), 1981 July 27; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Edwards (Box 15, Folder 14 [39153013991833])
  - English, Charles (6 pp.), 1981 July 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/English (Box 15, Folder 15 [39153013991999])
  - Engram, Georgia (24 pp.), 1981 July 28; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Engram (Box 15, Folder 16 [39153013992153])
  - Fisher, Peter (25 pp.), 1981 October 6; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Fisher (Box 15, Folder 17 [39153013992310])
  - Gee, Harry (22 pp.), 1981 June 15; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gee (Box 15, Folder 18 [39153013992328])
  - Gertsch, Lee (41 pp.), 1981 October 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gertsch (Box 15, Folder 19 [39153013992161])
  - Gibbons, Alice (16 pp.)
  - Gilbert, Bruce (57 pp.), 1981 June 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gilbert (Box 15, Folder 21 [39153013992005])
  - Gomez, William (36 pp.), 1981 July 7; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gomez (Box 15, Folder 22 [39153013991841])
  - Gorman, Frank (17 pp.), 1981 June 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gorman (Box 15, Folder 23 [39153013991858])
  - Graeber, George (27 pp.), 1981 June 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Graeber (Box 15, Folder 24 [39153013992013])
  - Grange, Sandy (18 pp.), 1981 July 1; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Grange (Box 15, Folder 25 [39153013992179])
  - Green, George (27 pp.), 1981 June 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Green (Box 15, Folder 26 [39153013992336])
  - Greenberg, Martin (16 pp.), 1981 June 3; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Greenberg (Box 15, Folder 27 [39153013992344])
  - Gregoire, Gail Costa (36 pp.), 1981 September 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gregoire (Box 15, Folder 28 [39153013992187])
  - Gregoire, Raymond (41 pp.), 1981 October 10; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/GregoireR (Box 15, Folder 29 [39153013992021])
  - Grills, Robert H. (41 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Grills (Box 15, Folder 30 [39153013991866])
  - Gumprecht, Gerry (37 pp.), 1981 May 27; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gumprecht (Box 16, Folder 1 [39153013991874])
  - Gutierrez, Art (20 pp.), 1981 July 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Gutierrez (Box 16, Folder 2 [39153013992039])
  - Hall, Norman and Renaud, "Rick" (34 pp.), 1982 March 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Hall (Box 16, Folder 3 [39153013992195])
  - Harrity, John (25 pp.), 1981 June 5; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Harrity (Box 16, Folder 4 [39153013992351])
  - Healy, Thomas (33pp., 48 pp.), 1981 September 30, 1981 October 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Healy (Box 16, Folder 5 [39153013992369])
  - Jackson, Minne (24 pp.), 1982 March 3; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Jackson (Box 16, Folder 6 [39153013992203])
  - Kiefer, Lou (30 pp.), 1981 June 3; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Kiefer (Box 16, Folder 7 [39153013992047])
  - Kleinschmidt, Arnold "Ike" (36 pp.), 1981 October 23; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Kleinschmidt (Box 16, Folder 8 [39153013991882])
  - Knybel, Charles (30 pp.), 1981 October 23; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Knybel (Box 16, Folder 9 [39153013991890])
  - Kosa, Gabriel (27 pp.), 1981 October 20; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Kosa (Box 16, Folder 10 [39153013992054])
  - Kwort, Kimberly (14 pp.), 1981 July 28; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Kwort (Box 16, Folder 11 [39153013992211])
  - Lacobelle, Fannie (20 pp.), 1982 March 3; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Lacobelle (Box 16, Folder 12 [39153013992377])
  - Lallier, Richard (19 pp.), 1981 July 29; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Lallier (Box 16, Folder 13 [39153013991908])
  - LaMantia, Josephine (20 pp.), 1981 June 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/LaMantia (Box 16, Folder 14 [39153013992062])
  - Lewis, Richard (29 pp.)
  - Linders, Ernest (33 pp.), 1981 November 10; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Linders (Box 16, Folder 16 [39153013992229])
  - Luddy, Christine (26 pp.), 1981 December 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Luddy (Box 16, Folder 17 [39153013992385])
  - Lukasiewski, Betty (15 pp.), 1982 February 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Lukasiewski (Box 16, Folder 18 [39153013992393])
  - Lyon, J. C. (34 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Lyon (Box 16, Folder 19 [39153013992237])
  - Maiorani, Mary (27 pp.), 1982 February 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Maiorani (Box 16, Folder 20 [39153013992245])
  - Martin, Dan (33 pp.), 1982 January 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Martin (Box 16, Folder 21 [39153013991916])
  - McClay, George (29 pp.)
  - McGrady, Thad (19 pp.), 1981 June 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/McGrady (Box 16, Folder 23 [39153013992070])
  - McGuire, Maura (20 pp.), 1981 June 23; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/McGuire (Box 16, Folder 24 [39153013992088])
  - McGuire, Patricia (29 pp.), 1981 July 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/McGuire_P (Box 16, Folder 25 [39153013991924])
  - McKinnon, Bernard (49 pp.), 1981 October 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/McKinnon (Box 16, Folder 26 [39153013991932])
  - McNeil, Dennis (18 pp.), 1982 April 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/McNeil (Box 16, Folder 27 [39153013992096])
  - Miller, Marvin (23 pp.), 1981 September 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Miller (Box 16, Folder 28 [39153013992401])
  - Nesselroth, Saul (24 pp.), 1981 June 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Nesselroth (Box 16, Folder 29 [39153013992252])
  - O'Connor, Julienne (26 pp.), 1981 July 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/O'Connor (Box 16, Folder 30 [39153013992419])
  - Opalenik, George (13 pp.), 1981 June 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Opalenik (Box 16, Folder 31 [39153013992427])
  - Otfinoski, Joseph (24 pp.), 1981 September 30; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Otfinoski_J (Box 16, Folder 32 [39153013992435])
  - Otfinoski, William (20 pp.), 1981 September 30; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Otfinoski_W (Box 17, Folder 1 [39153013992260])
  - Pampel, August (6 pp.), 1981 August 26; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Pampel (Box 17, Folder 2 [39153013992278])
  - Pappas, Adeline (17 pp.), 1981 December 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Pappas (Box 17, Folder 3 [39153013992104])
  - Patrick, James (27 pp.), 1981 September15; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Patrick (Box 17, Folder 4 [39153013992112])
  - Patterson, Edward (23 pp.), 1981 November 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Patterson (Box 17, Folder 5 [39153013991940])
  - Pelosi, Tony (36 pp.), 1981 May 27; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Pelosi (Box 17, Folder 6 [39153013991957])
  - Piscetello, Anthony (31 pp.), 1981 June 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Piscetello (Box 17, Folder 7 [39153013991502])
  - Pluff, Claire (33 pp.), 1981 July 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Pluff (Box 17, Folder 8 [39153013991494])
  - Poulin, Martin (35 pp.), 1981 October 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Poulin (Box 17, Folder 9 [39153013991486])
  - Purdie, Cynthia (21 pp.), 1981 December 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Purdie (Box 17, Folder 10 [39153013991353])
  - Rak, Joe (24 pp.), 1982 January 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Rak (Box 17, Folder 11 [39153013991510])
  - Ramsey, Glenn (39 pp.), 1981 June 17; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ramsey (Box 17, Folder 12 [39153013991643])
  - Rayel, Mark (26 pp.), 1981 July 20; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Rayel (Box 17, Folder 13 [39153013991650])
  - Ricci, Carl J. (17 pp.), 1981 June 9; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ricci (Box 17, Folder 14 [39153013991668])
  - Ricciuti, Renato (29 pp.), 1981 May 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ricciuti (Box 17, Folder 15 [39153013991676])
  - Rondeau, Maurice (46 pp.), 1981 June 10; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Rondeau (Box 17, Folder 16 [39153013991684])
  - Rovero, Lorraine (24 pp.), 1981 December 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Rovero (Box 17, Folder 17 [39153013991528])
  - Rudis, William (33 pp.), 1981 May 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Rudis (Box 17, Folder 18 [39153013991361])
  - Ryan, Robert (23 pp.), 1981 July 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ryan (Box 17, Folder 19 [39153013991205])
  - Sagnella, Angelo (18 pp.), 1982 January 11; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Sagnella (Box 17, Folder 21 [39153013991700])
  - Salafia, Anthony (22 pp.), 1981 July 16; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Salafia (Box 17, Folder 22 [39153013991536])
  - Salerno, Mary (21 pp.), 1982 March 6; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Salerno (Box 17, Folder 23 [39153013991718])
  - Sanders, George T. (44 pp.)
  - Sanville, Robert (48 pp.), 1981 October 28; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Sanville (Box 17, Folder 25 [39153013991379])
  - Schmid, Arthur (17 pp.), 1981 August 11; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Schmid (Box 17, Folder 26 [39153013991544])
  - Scopino, Aldorigo (35 pp.), 1982 May 21; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Scopino (Box 17, Folder 27 [39153013991213])
  - Scott, George A. (22 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/scott (Box 17, Folder 28 [39153013991221])
  - Setty, Naran (20 pp.), 1981 July 24; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Setty (Box 17, Folder 29 [39153013991387])
  - Sicignamo, Antoinette (15 pp.), 1982 March 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Sicignamo (Box 17, Folder 30 [39153013991239])
  - Sienkiewicz, Joan (36 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Sienkiewicz (Box 17, Folder 31 [39153013991395])
  - Smith, William (16 pp.), 1981 October 23; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Smith (Box 17, Folder 32 [39153013991551])
  - Soucie, Judith (32 pp.), 1981 December 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Soucie (Box 18, Folder 1 [39153013991742])
  - Sposato, Joseph (14 pp.), 1981 May 29; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Sposato (Box 18, Folder 2 [39153013991759])
  - Stoltz, Greg (23 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Stoltz (Box 18, Folder 3 [39153013991767])
  - Tetreault, Ivan (21 pp.), 1981 September 11; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Tetreault (Box 18, Folder 5 [39153013991783])
  - Tierney, John (32 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Tierney (Box 18, Folder 6 [39153013991791])
  - Tisdale, Walter (34 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Tisdale (Box 18, Folder 7 [39153013991601])
  - Tracey, Esther (22 pp.), 1981 July 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Tracey (Box 18, Folder 8 [39153013991619])
  - Vecchio, Antoinette (14 pp.), 1982 March 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Vecchio (Box 18, Folder 9 [39153013991627])
  - Vernovai, Michael and Martin Greenberg (63 pp.), 1981 June 3; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/VernovaiGreenberg (Box 18, Folder 10 [39153013991635])
  - Vincent, Agnes (17 pp.), 1981 July 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Vincent (Box 18, Folder 11 [39153013991478])
  - Vitkus, Joseph (25 pp.), 1981 November 4; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Vitkus (Box 18, Folder 12 [39153013991445])
  - Ward, Hugh (15 pp.), 1981 May 28; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Ward (Box 18, Folder 13 [39153013991452])
  - West, Benjamin (41 pp.), 1981 June 25; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/West_B (Box 18, Folder 14 [39153013991460])
  - West, Teresa (16 pp.), 1981 June 25; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/West_T (Box 18, Folder 15 [39153013991312])
  - Wheeler, Phillip (20 pp.), 1981 August 21; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Wheeler_P (Box 18, Folder 16 [39153013991304])
  - Wheeler, Sam (25 pp.), 1982 February 4; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Wheeler_S (Box 18, Folder 17 [39153013991296])
  - Whitbeck, Elizabeth (30 pp.), 1981 July 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Whitbeck (Box 18, Folder 18 [39153013991288])
  - Yeremian, Charles (39 pp.), 1981 June 12; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Yeremain (Box 18, Folder 19 [39153013993078])
  - Yonush, William (15 pp.), 1981 August 18; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Yonush (Box 18, Folder 20 [39153013993060])
  - Zygmunt, Margaret (37 pp.), 1981 November 20; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Zygmunt (Box 18, Folder 21 [39153013993052])
  - Anonymous Worker 1 (16 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous1 (Box 18, Folder 22 [39153013993037])
  - Anonymous Worker 2 (29 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous2 (Box 18, Folder 23 [39153013993045])
  - Anonymous Worker 4 (22 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous4 (Box 18, Folder 24 [39153013993003])
  - Anonymous Worker 5 (23 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous5 (Box 18, Folder 25 [39153013993011])
  - Anonymous Worker 6 (15 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous6 (Box 18, Folder 26 [39153013993029])
  - Anonymous Worker 7 (17 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous7 (Box 18, Folder 27 [39153013992997])
  - Anonymous Worker 8 (17 pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous8 (Box 18, Folder 28 [39153013992971])
  - Anonymous Worker 9 (21pp.), 1982 January 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous9 (Box 18, Folder 29 [39153013992989])
  - Anonymous Worker 10 (21pp.), 1981 October 28; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous10 (Box 18, Folder 30 [39153013992963])
  - Anonymous Worker 11 (44pp.), 1982 March 1; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anonymous11 (Box 18, Folder 31 [39153013992922])
  - Telephone Worker 1 (17 pp.), 1982 September 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Telephone1 (Box 18, Folder 32 [39153013992955])
  - Telephone Worker 2 (22 pp.), 1982 September 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Telephone2 (Box 18, Folder 33 [39153013992930])
  - Telephone Worker 3 (33 pp.), 1982 September 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Telephone3 (Box 18, Folder 34 [39153013992948])
  - Telephone Worker 4 (25 pp.), 1982 September 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Telephone4 (Box 18, Folder 35 [39153013992765])
  - Telephone Worker 5 (34 pp.), 1982 September 14; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Telephone5 (Box 18, Folder 36 [39153013992773])
- Creating Connecticut's Modern General Assembly Oral History Project, 1996-1997 (Box 19)
  [Project Director: Morton Tenzer and Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Morton Tenzer. See also: Interviews listed under Connecticut General Assembly and Student Projects-Lisbeth H. Dizney.]
  - Abate, Ernest (51 pp.), 1997 March 20; 1984-0025/ModernGeneralAssembly/Abate (Box 19, Folder 1 [39153013990827])
  - Collins, Francis (45 pp.), 1996 November 12; 1984-0025/SeriesModernGeneralAssembly/Collins (Box 19, Folder 2 [39153013990678])
  - Marcus, Edward (31 pp.), 1996 December 19; 1984-0025/SeriesModernGeneralAssembly/Marcus (Box 19, Folder 3 [39153013990835])
  - Ogle, David (101 pp.), 1997 January 24; 1984-0025/SeriesModernGeneralAssembly/Ogle (Box 19, Folder 4 [39153013990991])
  - Rome, Lewis B. (31 pp.), 1996 December 16; 1984-0025/SeriesModernGeneralAssembly/Rome (Box 19, Folder 5 [39153013990983])
  - Schneller, Richard (41 pp.), 1996 December 6; 1984-0025/SeriesModernGeneralAssembly/Schneller (Box 19, Folder 6 [39153013990975])
- Foreign Interviews, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave. * Published in Journal of Urban History; ** Published in Urban History Review. See Also: Interviews listed under The Making of Urban History and Chinese Urbanization and Urban Planning and American Studies in China.]
  - Australia and New Zealand, 1977
    - Davison, G.* (24 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Davison (Box 20, Folder 1 [39153013990967])
    - Fairburn, Miles (31 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Fairburn (Box 20, Folder 2 [39153013991148])
    - Neutze, Max (23 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Neutze (Box 20, Folder 3 [39153013991130])
    - Pearson, David and Claire Hatfield (20 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/PearsonHatfield (Box 20, Folder 4 [39153013991122])
    - Spearritt, Peter (29 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Spearritt (Box 20, Folder 5 [39153013990959])
    - Stannage, Tom (23 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Stannage (Box 20, Folder 6 [39153013991114])
    - Thorns, David and Leslie Kilmartin (33 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/ThornsKilmartin (Box 20, Folder 7 [39153013990942])
  - Canada, 1978
    - Artibise, Alan** (33 pp.), 1984-0025/FoeregnInterviews/Artibise (Box 20, Folder 8 [39153013991106])
    - Bedarida, Francois* (interviewed in U.S.) (29 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Bedarida (Box 20, Folder 10 [39153013990934])
    - Briggs, Asa (34 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Briggs (Box 20, Folder 11 [39153013990926])
    - Checkland, Mr. and Mrs. S. G. (38 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Checkland (Box 20, Folder 12 [39153013991080])
    - Dyos, A. J. * (37 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Dyos (Box 20, Folder 13 [39153013990918])
    - Hammarstrom, Ingrid * (32 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Hammarstrom (Box 20, Folder 15 [39153013990900])
    - Stelter, Gilbert* (40 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesForeignInterviews/Stelter (Box 20, Folder 9 [39153013991098])
    - Sutcliff, Anthony* (63 pp.), 1984-0025/ForeignInterviews/Sutcliffe (Box 20, Folder 14 [39153013991072])
- G. Fox & Company, 2006-2008 (Box 22, Box 21)
  [The G. Fox & Co. and Fox family materials, including these oral history interviews, are in the collections of The Connecticut Historical Society. Funding for the oral history collection and production was generously provided by grants from The Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation Fund at the Hartford Foundation for Public Giving, The Prospect Fund, The Brookside Fund, and The Maple Tree Fund. Copies of these oral histories are available for personal/educational use only. Permission to publish must be obtained from the The Connecticut Historical Society. The interviews were conducted between 2006 and 2008.]
  - Aiello, Amadeo Michael (22 pp.), 2006 October 30; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Aiello (Box 21, Folder 1 [39153013990892])
  - Barry, Mary (36 pp.), 2006 October 30; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Barry (Box 21, Folder 2 [39153013991049])
  - Biancanelli, Joseph (38 pp.), 2006 September 12; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Biancanelli (Box 21, Folder 3 [39153013991031])
  - Black, Harry and Jack Litter (34 pp.), 2006 October 16; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/BlackLitter (Box 21, Folder 4 [39153013991023])
  - Blawie, Bruce (15 pp.), 2007 January 4; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Blawie_B (Box 21, Folder 5 [39153013990884])
  - Blawie, Roslyn (29 pp.), 2007 January 4; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Blawie_R (Box 21, Folder 6 [39153013990876])
  - Breer, Janice (17 pp.), 2007 January 30; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Breer (Box 21, Folder 7 [39153013990868])
  - Brutto, Carmelo (22 pp.), 2007 January 19; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Brutto (Box 21, Folder 8 [39153013991015])
  - Candels, Carl (32 pp.), 2006 December 20; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Candels (Box 21, Folder 9 [39153013990850])
  - Coburn, Thea (18 pp.), 2006 November 10; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Coburn (Box 21, Folder 10 [39153013991007])
  - Gordon, Fran (33 pp.), 2006 October 9; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Gordon (Box 21, Folder 11 [39153013990843])
  - Griffin, Delia (24 pp.), 2007 January 12; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Griffin (Box 21, Folder 12 [39153013991163])
  - Harman, Janice (17 pp.), 2006 November 3; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Harman (Box 21, Folder 13 [39153013991171])
  - Hazel, Eliza (14 pp.), 2007 January 24; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Hazel (Box 21, Folder 14 [39153013991189])
  - Kelly, Eunice (44 pp.), 2007 June 12; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Kelly (Box 21, Folder 15 [39153013991197])
  - Koopman, Dorothy (37 pp.), 2007 June 7; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Koopman (Box 21, Folder 16 [39153013991320])
  - Koopman, Rena (38 pp.), 2007 June 7; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Koopman_R (Box 21, Folder 17 [39153013991338])
  - Koplowitz, Shirley (34 pp.), 2007 March 27; 1984-0025/SeriesGFoxCompany/Koplowitz (Box 21, Folder 18 [39153013991346])
  - Ladd, Betty (28 pp.), 2007 June 18; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Ladd (Box 22, Folder 1 [39153013991403])
  - Laraia, Frank (48 pp.), 2006 August 28; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Laraia (Box 22, Folder 2 [39153013991569])
  - Lichtenbaum, Jay (40 pp.), 2007 January 11; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Lichtenbaum (Box 22, Folder 3 [39153013991726])
  - Martucci, Jennie (33 pp.), 2008 January 29; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Martucci (Box 22, Folder 4 [39153013991734])
  - Mullen, Paul (22 pp.), 2006 October 6; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Mullen (Box 22, Folder 5 [39153013991577])
  - Neimark, Ira (43 pp.), 2006 September 18; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Neimark (Box 22, Folder 6 [39153013991411])
  - Pontillo, John (30 pp.), 2007 January 17; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Pontillo (Box 22, Folder 7 [39153013991254])
  - Raptopoulos, Fanny (48 pp.), 2008 April 10; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Raptopoulos (Box 22, Folder 8 [39153013991262])
  - Riley, Irene (30 pp.), 2006 November 30; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Riley (Box 22, Folder 9 [39153013991270])
  - Sobol, Irma (29 pp.), 2005 September 25; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Sobol (Box 22, Folder 10 [39153013991429])
  - Tine, Joseph (23 pp.), 2006 December 21; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Tine (Box 22, Folder 11 [39153013991437])
  - Uccello, Antonina (Ann) (42 pp.), 2006 October 23; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Uccello (Box 22, Folder 12 [39153013991585])
  - Witham, Philip (36 pp.), 2006 September 5; 1984-0025/GFoxandCompany/Witham (Box 22, Folder 13 [39153013991593])
- Goodwin Forest Oral History, 2006-2008 (Box 23)
- Gravetending in the New Mansfield Cemetery, 1997-1998 (Box 24)
  [Project Director: Leslie Frank. Interviews By: Leslie Frank.]
  - Ahern, Alice (Storrs Cemetery) (28 pp.), 1997 November 25; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Ahern (Box 24, Folder 1 [39153013992807])
  - Bailey, Dorothy (18 pp.), 1998 February 27; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Bailey (Box 24, Folder 2 [39153013992815])
  - Cole, Charles (28 pp.), 1997 November 19; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Cole (Box 24, Folder 3 [39153013992823])
  - Hansen, Kris (12 pp.), 1997 October 27; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Hansen (Box 24, Folder 4 [39153013992831])
  - Levine, Ronnie (31 pp.), 1998 February 20; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Levine (Box 24, Folder 5 [39153013992849])